{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is Prime Minister of the United Kingdom?",
      "choices": [
        "David Cameron",
        "Gordon Brown",
        "Winston Churchill",
        "Tony Blair"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the father of Geometry?",
      "choices": [
        "Aristotle",
        "Euclid",
        "Pythagoras",
        "Kepler"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The Homolographic projection has the correct representation of",
      "choices": [
        "shape",
        "area",
        "baring",
        "distance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The hazards of radiation belts include",
      "choices": [
        "deterioration of electronic circuits",
        "damage of solar cells of spacecraft",
        "adverse effect on living organisms",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The great Victoria Desert is located in",
      "choices": [
        "Canada",
        "West Africa",
        "Australia",
        "North America"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is tropical grassland?",
      "choices": [
        "Taiga",
        "Savannah",
        "Pampas",
        "Prairies"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "With the disintegration of USSR in end 1991, comprised of ____ Union Republics.",
      "choices": [
        "15",
        "10",
        "5",
        "25"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The temperature increases rapidly after",
      "choices": [
        "ionosphere",
        "exosphere",
        "stratosphere",
        "troposphere"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The largest gold producing country in the world(in 2006) is",
      "choices": [
        "China",
        "Canada",
        "South Africa",
        "USA"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The largest country of the world by geographical area is",
      "choices": [
        "Russia",
        "Vatican City",
        "Australia",
        "USA"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    }
  ]
}
